▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 第二轮
斯瓦泰克 6-3 6-0 阿朗戈 · 赛后场上采访
It's long.
出界了
Well, it was virtually perfect second set
这第二盘打得几乎完美
for Iga.
斯瓦泰克
Absolutely flying.
整个人像在飞
Arango made a good start.
阿朗戈开局不错
the better start
开局是她更好
and was a break up early on but after
早早破了一个发球局 可那之后
that break she made just one more game
她只再拿下了一局
and in the end a bagel in the second set
第二盘最后是六比零
that looked likely I have to say
说实话这个结果早看得出
from the second point no kidding of this set
从这一盘的第二分起
and she just would not release
她一点都没有
the throttle wasn't expected to win
松开油门 本来也没人看好她
and once again she gets just three games
她又一次只拿到三局
as she did in the first meeting
和两人第一次交手时一样
between the two
那一次
on the US hard courts last year
是去年在美国的硬地上
through the third
打到第三盘
as a big Iga Swiatek fan I
作为斯瓦泰克的铁杆球迷
am and so are the fans here.
我是 在场的观众也是
It was really cool
特别过瘾
to watch you ease your way into that match
看着你一点点进入这场比赛
and find your stride.
找到自己的节奏
You must be happy
今天这场表现
with your performance today.
你一定很满意吧
Yeah, for sure. You know,
当然
it was necessary for me to get
我必须先
to know the court and find the rhythm
熟悉这块场地 找到节奏
because it's much different than in Toronto.
这里和多伦多很不一样
So, I'm happy that, you know,
所以我挺高兴
I was patient and I came back
我沉住了气 第二盘回来时
for a second set knowing what to improve
已经知道该改什么
and it went pretty smooth from that.
之后就打得很顺
How special did it feel to walk out
今天以卫冕冠军的身份
on the court today as defending champion
走上这块球场
and feeling the love?
感觉有多特别
All the Polish fans here today,
今天来的这么多波兰球迷
all the Cincinnati fans, do you hear?
辛辛那提的球迷 你听得见吗
I know you have headphones
我知道你戴着耳机
on, so I'm not sure if you hear it,
不确定你听不听得到
but can you feel it
但隔着耳机
through the headphones?
你感觉得到吗
There's a lot of love for you here.
这里有好多人喜欢你
The music is pretty loud, but I still can hear.
音乐挺响 但我还是听得见
So, thank you guys for the support
谢谢大家的支持
and the nice welcome.
也谢谢这么好的欢迎
I love, you know, coming back here,
我很喜欢回到这里
especially now that the site is so beautiful
尤其现在这个场地这么漂亮
and, brand new, you know.
全都是新的
I'm really happy to be back
能回来我真的很开心
and I think a lot of people were excited
我想很多人也都盼着
to come back after last year.
去年之后再回到这儿
All right, next up is Maria Sakkari.
好 下一轮是萨卡里
You know her game very well.
你很了解她的打法
She knows yours. She's one
她也了解你
of the few players
这些年能让你难受的球员不多
who has given you a hard time in the past,
她是其中一个
but what do you what are we in store
那下一场
for when we see that next match?
我们能期待什么
Well, for sure. She's a really experienced
那当然 她经验非常丰富
and great player, great competitor.
球打得好 也很能拼
So, for sure it's going to be tough.
所以肯定不好打
I'll just, you know, prepare tactically
我会把战术准备好
and I'll be ready.
然后做好准备
We already played this season,
这个赛季我们已经交过手
so obviously we know each other's game.
彼此的球路都清楚
It's going to be about, you know,
到时候就看
who brings better quality.
谁能打出更高的质量
So for sure it's going to be a challenge.
所以这肯定是一场硬仗
All right, one thing I'd like to say
好 最后我想说一句
to defending champions and players
对卫冕冠军 也对每一位
who have won this tournament
在这里夺过冠的球员
before, welcome home.
欢迎回家
We love that you're here in Mason, Ohio.
很高兴你来到俄亥俄的梅森
Ladies and gentlemen, Iga.
女士们先生们 斯瓦泰克